brainybetty.com 2012-05-03

# Brainy Betty Privacy Policy

|  | 

> **PRIVACY POLICY**
> 
> This privacy policy was last updated on 03/20/2012. 
> 
> Brainy Betty, Inc.,  and its  other web holdings (collectively referred to as ""we", "us" or "our", as applicable) are committed to maintaining the privacy of personal information that you provide to us when using our respective web sites. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat personal information received about you when you visit the Brainy Betty, Inc. Web Sites. 
> 
> **Information Collected**
> 
> Web Site Usage Information: We automatically collect IP addresses and web site usage information from you when you visit our Web Sites. This information helps us in evaluating how our visitors use and navigate the Web Sites **on an aggregate basis** , including the number and frequency of visitors to each page of the Web Sites, and the length of their visits. 
> 
>   * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. 
>   * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. 
>   * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [ Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 
> 

> 
> Special Features: When you use purchase any on our Web Sites, we may collect personally identifiable information from you that may include your name, address, e-mail address, credit-card number and facts about your interests and similar information. This information will NEVER be shared or sold. This is our commitment to you.
> 
> Surveys and Forms: We may conduct occasional online surveys or ask you to fill in forms. ** **
> 
>  ****
> 
> **How We Use Information Collected**
> 
> We may use information that you provide us in the following ways: 
> 
>   * For the purposes for which you specifically provided the information, for example, when you request that additional information be sent to you, we will use your personal information to process your request. 
>   * To send you e-mail notifications about our new or existing services or to otherwise contact you. 
>   * To allow us to personalize the content and advertising that you and others see based on personal characteristics or preferences. 
>   * To enhance existing features or develop new features, products and services. 
>   * To provide advertisers and other third parties with **aggregate** information **only** about our user base and usage patterns. 
> 

> 
> We may disclose and use personally identifiable information in special circumstances where it is necessary to enforce our Terms of Use (for example, when necessary to protect our intellectual property rights) or when we, in our sole discretion, believe it is necessary or appropriate, in connection with a sale or transfer of some or all of our assets in the Brainy Betty, Inc. Web Sites. We may also disclose personally identifiable information when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires us to do so. As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In transactions such as these, customer information is generally one of the transferred business assets. Moreover, in the unlikely event that we or one of our sites are acquired, customer information may be one of the transferred assets. 
> 
> Except as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy, we will not share your personally identifiable information outside of Brainy Betty, Inc. unless you "opt in" to having your personally identifiable information shared with a company that is not affiliated with us. 
> 
> ****
> 
> **Links to Third Party Web Sites**
> 
> We may make third party content or services from other web sites available to you from links located on the Brainy Betty, Inc. Web Sites. These other web sites are not subject to this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you review the terms of use and privacy policy at each such web site to determine how that site protects your privacy. We are not responsible for the content of those web sites or the actions of third party web site operators. 
> 
> **Security**
> 
> The personally identifiable information we collect about you is stored in limited access servers. We will maintain reasonable safeguards to protect the security of these servers and your personally identifiable information. 
> 
> ****
> 
> **Exclusions**
> 
> Any submissions that you make to any public areas of the Brainy Betty, Inc. Web Sites including but not limited to, chat services, bulletin boards, reviews, (collectively "Public Areas") will be public and will not be subject to this Privacy Policy. We do not control, and are not responsible for, the actions of other users of the Brainy Betty Web Sites with respect to any information you post in Public Areas. In addition, information that you submit to Public Areas may be collected and used by others to send you unsolicited messages and for other purposes.
> 
> ****
> 
> **Policy Modifications**
> 
> We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically. 
> 
> Thank you for your trust in our company. We will work diligently to ensure that we maintain that trust.
> 
> Nan Shastry, CEO - Brainy Betty, Inc.  
  
---
